[
    {
    "question": "What is the first letter of the word 'Apple'?",
    "choices": [
      "A",
      "P",
      "E",
      "L"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "category": "Letters",
    "versions": [
      "What is the first letter of the word 'Apple'?",
      "What is the opening letter of the alphabet for the word 'Apple'?",
      "What is the initial character of the word 'Apple'?",
      "What is the initial letter of the word 'Apple'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الحرف الاول من كلمه \"Apple\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الحرف الافتتاحي للابجدية لكلمه \"Apple\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الشخصية الاولية لكلمه \"Apple\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الحرف الاولي لكلمه \"Apple\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ا",
      "ص",
      "هـ",
      "ل"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "ا",
    "category_ar": "حروف"
  },{
    "question": "Which word starts with the letter 'D'?",
    "choices": [
      "Car",
      "Dog",
      "Apple",
      "Sun"
    ],
    "answer": "Dog",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "Which word starts with the letter 'D'?",
      "What is the word that starts with the letter 'D'?",
      "What is the first letter of a word?",
      "What is a word that begins with the letter 'D'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اي كلمه تبدا بالحرف \"د\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الكلمه اللي تبدا بالحرف \"د\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الحرف الاول من الكلمه؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الكلمه اللي تبدا بالحرف \"د\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "سيارة",
      "كلب",
      "تفاحة",
      "شمس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "كلب",
    "category_ar": "كلمات"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the missing word? 'The cat is ____ the box.'",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "on",
      "under",
      "at"
    ],
    "answer": "in",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "What is the missing word? 'The cat is ____ the box.'",
      "What is the missing word in this sentence? 'The cat is ____ the box.",
      "What is the missing letter? 'The cat is ____ the box.",
      "What is the missing letter? 'The cat is ____ the box.'"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الكلمه المفقودة؟ \"القط هـو ____ الصندوق.\"",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الكلمه المفقودة في هـذهـ الجُملة؟ \"القط هـو ____ الصندوق.",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الحرف المفقودة؟ \"القط هـو ____ الصندوق.",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الحرف المفقودة؟ \"القط هـو ____ الصندوق.\""
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في",
      "على",
      "تحت",
      "في"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في",
    "category_ar": "جُمل"
  },{
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence:",
    "choices": [
      "I like play",
      "I playing",
      "I like to play",
      "Like I play"
    ],
    "answer": "I like to play",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "Choose the correct sentence:",
      "What is the appropriate sentence?",
      "Which sentence is correct?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اختر الجُملة الصحيحة:",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الجُملة المناسبة؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الجُملة الصحيحة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "انا احب اللعب",
      "العب",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: احب اللعب",
      "كانني العب"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: احب اللعب",
    "category_ar": "جُمل"
  },{
    "question": "What is the plural of 'cat'?",
    "choices": [
      "Cats",
      "Cated",
      "Cat",
      "Cattes"
    ],
    "answer": "Cats",
    "category": "Words",
    "versions": [
      "What is the plural of 'cat'?",
      "What is the plural of the word 'cat'?",
      "How do you make 'cat' plural?",
      "Can you tell me the plural of 'cat'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو صيغة \"القط\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو صيغة كلمه \"القط\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: كيف تجعل الجمع \"القط\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: هـل يمكن ان تخبرني بصيغة \"القط\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "القطط",
      "cated",
      "قطة",
      "Cattes"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "القطط",
    "category_ar": "كلمات"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choose the correct article: ___ apple",
    "choices": [
      "A",
      "An",
      "The",
      "Some"
    ],
    "answer": "An",
    "category": "Sentences",
    "versions": [
      "Choose the correct article: ___ apple",
      "Which article is appropriate: apple ___?",
      "What is the right choice: apple ___?",
      "Which article is appropriate: __ apple?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اختر المقالة الصحيحة: ___ Apple",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اي مقالة مناسبة: Apple ___؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الخيار الصحيح: Apple ___؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اي مقال مناسب: __ Apple؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ا",
      "و",
      "ال",
      "بعض"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "و",
    "category_ar": "جُمل"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the last letter in 'Dog'?",
    "choices": [
      "D",
      "G",
      "O",
      "T"
    ],
    "answer": "G",
    "category": "Letters",
    "versions": [
      "What is the last letter in 'Dog'?",
      "What is the concluding letter of 'Dog'?",
      "What is the letter that completes 'Dog'?",
      "What is the final letter in 'Dog'?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الحرف الاخيرة في \"الكلب\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي خطاب \"الكلب\" الختامي؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الحرف اللي تكمل \"كلب\"؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الحرف الاخيرة في \"الكلب\"؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "د",
      "ز",
      "س",
      "ر"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "ز",
    "category_ar": "حروف"
  },{
    "question": "What do you do with a book?",
    "choices": [
      "Eat",
      "Read",
      "Throw",
      "Sit"
    ],
    "answer": "Read",
    "category": "Comprehension",
    "versions": [
      "What do you do with a book?",
      "How do you utilize a book?",
      "How do you use a book?",
      "What is your approach to using a book?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ماذا تفعل مع كتاب؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: كيف تستخدم كتابًا؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: كيف تستخدم كتاب؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو نهـجك في استخدام كتاب؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "ياكل",
      "يقرا",
      "يرمي",
      "يجلس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "يقرا",
    "category_ar": "فهـم"
  },{
    "question": "What do you do at night?",
    "choices": [
      "Eat breakfast",
      "Sleep",
      "Go to school",
      "Play in sun"
    ],
    "answer": "Sleep",
    "category": "Comprehension",
    "versions": [
      "What do you do at night?",
      "What activities do you engage in during the night?",
      "How do you spend your evenings?",
      "What activities do you engage in during the evening?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ماذا تفعل في الليل؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الانشطة اللي تشارك فيهـا خلال الليل؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: كيف تقضي امسياتك؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الانشطة اللي تشارك فيهـا خلال المساء؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "تناول وجبة الإفطار",
      "ينام",
      "اذهـب إلى المدرسة",
      "العب في الشمس"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "ينام",
    "category_ar": "فهـم"
  },{
    "question": "How much is 18 - 9?",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "9",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "How much is 18 - 9?",
      "What is the value of 18 raised to the power of 9?",
      "What is the quotient when 18 is added to 9?",
      "What is the sum of 18 and 9?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: كم هـو 18 - 9؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي قيمة 18 رفعت إلى سلطة 9؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الحاصل عند إضافة 18 إلى 9؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو مجموع 18 و 9؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "9",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },{
    "question": "What is 20 ÷ 5?",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 20 ÷ 5?",
      "What is the result of 20 to the power of 5?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 20 by 5?",
      "What is the answer when 20 is divided by 5?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو 20 ÷ 5؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي نتيجة 20 إلى قوة 5؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي نتيجة ضرب 20 × 5؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الإجابة عندما ينقسم 20 على 5؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "4",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },{
    "question": "How much is 10 - 7?",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "How much is 10 - 7?",
      "What is the total of 10 and 7?",
      "What is the answer to 10 multiplied by 7?",
      "What is the numerical worth of 10 to 7?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: كم هـو 10 - 7؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو مجموع 10 و 7؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الإجابة على 10 مضروبة في 7؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي القيمة العددية من 10 إلى 7؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "3",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },{
    "question": "What is 16 ÷ 4?",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "Math",
    "versions": [
      "What is 16 ÷ 4?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 16 by 4?",
      "What is the result of multiplying 16 by itself 16 times?",
      "What is the answer when 16 is divided by 4?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو 16 ÷ 4؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي نتيجة ضرب 16 × 4؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي نتيجة ضرب 16 بنفس 16 مرة؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الإجابة عندما ينقسم 16 على 4؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "4",
    "category_ar": "الرياضيات"
  },{
    "question": "What word tells you something is lower than another object?",
    "choices": [
      "Above",
      "Under",
      "Next to",
      "Behind"
    ],
    "answer": "Under",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What word tells you something is lower than another object?",
      "What is the term for indicating that something is situated below another thing?",
      "What is the term for indicating that something is situated beneath another thing?",
      "What is the term used to describe something that is smaller than another thing?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـي الكلمه اللي تخبرك بشيء اقل من كائن آخر؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو مصطلح الإشارة إلى ان هـناك شيئًا ما اسفل شيء آخر؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو مصطلح الإشارة إلى ان هـناك شيئًا ما يقع تحت شيء آخر؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو المصطلح المستخدم لوصف شيء اصغر من شيء آخر؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "فوق",
      "تحت",
      "بجوار",
      "خلف"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "تحت",
    "category_ar": "الوعي المكاني"
},{
    "question": "Where is your nose?",
    "choices": [
      "On your hand",
      "On your arm",
      "On your face",
      "On your foot"
    ],
    "answer": "On your face",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is your nose?",
      "What is the location of your nasal cavity?",
      "Can you tell me the location of your nose?",
      "Can you tell me where your nose is located?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين انفك؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو موقع تجويف الانف؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: هـل يمكن ان تخبرني موقع انفك؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: هـل يمكن ان تخبرني اين يقع انفك؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على يدك",
      "على ذراعك",
      "على وجهـك",
      "على قدمك"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "على وجهـك",
    "category_ar": "الوعي المكاني"
  },{
    "question": "If a ball is between two chairs, where is it?",
    "choices": [
      "On the chairs",
      "Outside the chairs",
      "Between the chairs",
      "Under the chairs"
    ],
    "answer": "Between the chairs",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "If a ball is between two chairs, where is it?",
      "Where can a ball be found if it is placed between two chairs?",
      "Where is the location of the ball that is situated between two chairs?",
      "Where can a ball be found if it is between two chairs?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، الترجمة: إذا كانت الكرة بين كرسيين ، فاين هـي؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين يمكن العثور على الكرة إذا تم وضعهـا بين كرسيين؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين هـو موقع الكرة اللي تقع بين كرسيين؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين يمكن العثور على الكرة إذا كانت بين كرسيين؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الكراسي",
      "خارج الكراسي",
      "بين الكراسي",
      "تحت الكراسي"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "بين الكراسي",
    "category_ar": "الوعي المكاني"
  },{
    "question": "Where is the teacher usually standing?",
    "choices": [
      "Behind the students",
      "In front of the class",
      "Outside the school",
      "Next to the door"
    ],
    "answer": "In front of the class",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the teacher usually standing?",
      "What is the usual location of the teacher's desk?",
      "Where can I find the teacher's usual location?",
      "What is the usual location of the teacher?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين يقف المعلم عادة؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الموقع المعتاد لمكتب المعلم؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين يمكنني ان اجد الموقع المعتاد للمعلم؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الموقع المعتاد للمعلم؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "وراء الطلاب",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: امام الفصل",
      "خارج المدرسة",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: بجانب الباب"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: امام الفصل",
    "category_ar": "الوعي المكاني"
  },{
    "question": "What is 'inside' the pencil case?",
    "choices": [
      "The chair",
      "The pen",
      "The wall",
      "The book"
    ],
    "answer": "The pen",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "What is 'inside' the pencil case?",
      "What is contained within the inside of the pencil case?",
      "What lies inside the pencil case?",
      "What can be found inside the pencil case?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو \"داخل\" حالة القلم الرصاص؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الوارد في الجزء الداخلي من علبة القلم الرصاص؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما الذي يكمن داخل علبة القلم الرصاص؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما الذي يمكن العثور عليهـ داخل علبة القلم الرصاص؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "الكرسي",
      "القلم",
      "الجدار",
      "الكتاب"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "القلم",
    "category_ar": "الوعي المكاني"
  },{
    "question": "If the box is in front of the boy, where is the boy?",
    "choices": [
      "Behind the box",
      "Inside the box",
      "On top of the box",
      "Next to the box"
    ],
    "answer": "Behind the box",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "If the box is in front of the boy, where is the boy?",
      "Where can the boy be found if he is in the box in front of him?",
      "Where is the boy if he is in front of the box?",
      "In the box, where is the boy located if he is in front of it?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: إذا كان الصندوق امام الصبي ، فاين الصبي؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين يمكن العثور على الصبي إذا كان في الصندوق امامهـ؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين هـو الصبي إذا كان امام الصندوق؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: في الصندوق ، اين يقع الصبي إذا كان امامهـ؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "خلف الصندوق",
      "داخل الصندوق",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اعلى الصندوق",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: بجانب الصندوق"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "خلف الصندوق",
    "category_ar": "الوعي المكاني"
  },{
    "question": "Where is the clock usually placed in a classroom?",
    "choices": [
      "On the floor",
      "Under the table",
      "On the wall",
      "In the drawer"
    ],
    "answer": "On the wall",
    "category": "Spatial Awareness",
    "versions": [
      "Where is the clock usually placed in a classroom?",
      "What is the customary placement of the clock in a classroom?",
      "What is the typical placement of the clock in a classroom?",
      "In what area of a classroom is the clock usually located?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين يتم وضع الساعة عادة في الفصل الدراسي؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الموضع العرفي على مدار الساعة في الفصل الدراسي؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: ما هـو الموضع النموذجي على مدار الساعة في الفصل الدراسي؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: في اي مجال من الفصول الدراسية تقع الساعة عادة؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "على الارض",
      "تحت الطاولة",
      "على الحائط",
      "في الدرج"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "على الحائط",
    "category_ar": "الوعي المكاني"
  },{
    "question": "If a person is standing behind you, where are they?",
    "choices": [
      "In front of you",
      "Next to you",
      "Behind you",
      "Above you"
    ],
    "answer": "Behind you",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If a person is standing behind you, where are they?",
      "If someone is behind you, where is the person?",
      "If someone is following you, where is the person?",
      "Where is the person standing in your way?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: إذا كان الشخص يقف خلفك ، فاين هـم؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: إذا كان شخص ما وراءك ، فاين الشخص؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: إذا كان شخص ما يتابعك ، فاين هـو الشخص؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: اين يقف الشخص في طريقك؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: امامك",
      "بجوارك",
      "خلفك",
      "فوقك"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "خلفك",
    "category_ar": "الاتجاهـ"
  },{
    "question": "If you're facing east and turn right, where are you facing?",
    "choices": [
      "South",
      "North",
      "West",
      "East"
    ],
    "answer": "South",
    "category": "Directionality",
    "versions": [
      "If you're facing east and turn right, where are you facing?",
      "When you turn right and face east, where is the destination?",
      "If you turn right and face east, where do you currently stand?",
      "When you turn right facing east, where do you see?"
    ],
    "versions_ar": [
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: إذا كنت تواجهـ الشرق وانتقل يمينًا ، فاين تواجهـ؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: عندما تتجهـ يمينًا وتواجهـ شرقًا ، اين هـي الوجهـة؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: إذا تحولت يمينًا وتواجهـ شرقًا ، فاين تقف حاليًا؟",
      "في سياق التعليم ، ترجمة: عندما تدور يمينًا في مواجهـة الشرق ، اين ترى؟"
    ],
    "choices_ar": [
      "جنوب",
      "شمال",
      "الغرب",
      "شرق"
    ],
    "answer_ar": "جنوب",
    "category_ar": "الاتجاهـ"
  }
]